He will do anything to protect his family.
Domestic Disturbance is a thriller, crime, mystery
film directed by Harold Becker.
Frank Morrison is a divorced father with a 12-year-old son, Danny.
His ex-wife Susan and son Danny now live with Rick Barnes, Susan's new husband.
Danny, who has a reputation for telling lies, accuses
his stepfather of committing a murder.
Initially, no one believes his accusations, but then Frank becomes
convinced and is the only one who believes him.
Now, the father Danny trusts must protect him from the stepfather he fears.
Frank Morrison, played by John Travolta.
Danny Morrison, played by Matt O'Leary.
Rick Barnes, played by Vince Vaughn.
Susan, played by Teri Polo.
Sgt. Edgar Stevens, played by Ruben Santiago-Hudson.
Ray Coleman, played by Steve Buscemi.
Domestic Disturbance is a 2001 American psychological thriller film directed by Harold Becker and
starring John Travolta, Vince Vaughn, Teri Polo, Steve Buscemi, and Matt O'Leary.
The film is about a divorced father who discovers his
son's new stepfather is a murderer.
The film was released by Paramount Pictures on November 2, 2001 to negative reviews from critics
and was a box office bomb, grossing $54.2 million against a $75 million budget.
The film explores themes of maryland, stepfather,
murder, witness to murder, newlywed.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.